翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
We'll get to writing our first Java program in a moment.
稍后我们将开始编写第一个 Java 程序
But let me give a couple of meta points.
在此之前我先说几个要点
First, any code I write in these videos is going to be on the site.
首先，我在视频中的代码都可以在网站中找到
If you click these code links, it will bring you to a Github repository that will have all the things I write so you experiment with it.
点击链接会跳转到 GitHub 存储库，包含了我写的所有内容
So if you want to know, oh, what happens if I tweak this little bit,
如果你想知道稍微修改一下代码的运行结果
you can download the code, run it, and experiment to your heart's content.
可以下载代码自行尝试
And second meta point, if you already know Java,
第二点是如果你已经了解 Java 了
you may want to double speed the rest of any of these videos or even skip them.
可以倍速播放这部分视频或直接跳过
Because it's just the very basics of Java.
因为这些知识很基础
Now this class is going to move through Java very fast
这门课关于 Java 的内容进度会很快
because we're assuming you already have a substantial amount of programming experience.
因为我们假设你已经有了大量的编程经验
And we're just going to get you acquainted with the most salient features of the language.
我们只是想让你了解一下这种语言最突出的特性
And now it is time to write our first program in Java.
现在我们编写第一个 Java 程序
So I'm going to show on the left how we can print out the phrase Hello world in Python.
我将在左边展示如何用 Python 打印 Hello world
When I run this code, it prints out Hello world.
运行此代码会打印出 Hello world
You don't have to understand Python.
您不必理解 Python
It's not a prerequisite for this class.
这不是这门课的必修
But the point here is simply to say that it's a pretty simple language.
不过讲起来也不难，这门语言很简单
Like if I want to print Hello world, that's all I get.
比如我想打印 Hello world 就能得到
By contrast, in Java, well, I'll just try and run the code in Java.
那么用 Java 运行代码
And it's no surprise that in Java,
毫不奇怪
trying to copy and paste Python code into the Java environment is not going to work well.
将 Python 代码复制到 Java 环境中无法运行
Instead I get this error-- class, interface or enum expected.
我得到这个错误...需要类、接口或枚举
So what this compiler is trying to tell us is, I'm expecting a class.
编译器告诉我们它需要一个类
That's an important feature of the Java language,
这是 Java 语言的一个重要特性
that all code must live inside of a class and that it doesn't make sense to have code that is not part of one.
所有代码都必须在一个类中，类之外的代码毫无意义
So to declare a class in Java, what I'm going to do is say public class,
因此要定义一个类，public class...
and in this case I'm going to give a name to the class, HelloWorld.
然后给这个类起一个名字 HelloWorld
And when I've done now I've created a class, which is a thing that Java requires me to do.
这样我就创建了一个 Java 必需的类
I try running this.
尝试运行一下
And I get, main method not found in class Hello world.
报错了，HelloWorld 类中没有 main 方法
Please define the main method as--
请将 main 方法定义为...
so this right here is about the most useful error message ever.
这就是最有用的错误信息
Often error messages and compilers are mysterious.
错误信息和编译器通常是神秘的
This one's saying please copy and paste this into your code.
我们将这段代码复制到上面
And so I have.
就像这样
And we don't know what this means yet, as we're learning.
我们是初学者，还不知道它的意思
But it's something we are going to happen in all of our programs for quite a while.
但在相当长的一段时间里我们在所有程序中都要这样写
And what this does for us is--
这会为我们...
well, I'll try running it for you.
运行一下
What you see is if I try running this now, the compiler is happy.
可以看到运行这段代码，编译器很高兴
This is a valid class.
这是一个有效的类
It has this thing, whatever that is.
有了这段代码，不管它是什么意思
We run it. And now finally, nothing happens.
运行后终于没有报错了
So in other words, what I'm written on the right,
换句话说，右边写的这些
this is the Java equivalent of this program in Python.
就是 Python 在 Java 中的等价代码
They do the same thing.
他们做的事情一样
So if I want to actually cause it to print something out,
如果我想让它打印出一些东西
this is where the code is going to go.
这就是要写代码的地方
How do I do that?
该怎么做呢？
So what I'm going to do is copy and paste the Hello World.
复制粘贴 Hello World
But in Java, it's not just print.
但在 Java 中，print 是不够的
It's system dot out dot print ln Hello world.
应该是  System.out.println("hello world")
And when I run this, finally I get Hello world.
运行这个程序终于得到了 hello world
So that's a most basic program.
这是一个最基础的程序
Now one famous aspect of Java is that it's a little verbose.
Java 的冗长很出名
And so this might seem a little intimidating.
这可能看起来有点吓人
But it shouldn't be.
但其实不是的
We're just going to have to accept that there are certain things that are in Java programs that we won't understand quite yet.
Java 程序中确实有一些我们还不太了解的东西
Let's try and enumerate a little bit.
让我们试着列举一下
So down here I'm writing a comment.
我在下面这里写一下注释
This is just information.
这些仅是信息
I put it between these symbols, which means the compiler won't try and run it.
把它放在这些符号之间，意味着编译器不会运行它
So I'm going to make some notes.
我写一些笔记
All code in Java must be part of a class.
Java 中的所有代码都必须是类的一部分
We delimit the beginning and end of segments of code using that symbol
我们使用这两个符号分隔代码块的开头和结尾
and that symbol that all statements in Java must end in a semicolon.
Java 中的所有语句都必须以分号结束
So what I mean by that is I put a semicolon here.
我在这里写了一个分号
You might not have noticed.
你可能没有注意到
If I delete this and try running it,
如果我删除它后运行
the compiler will yell at me and say, semicolon expected.
编译器会报错说需要分号
And then lastly, we had code inside of--
最后
for code to run, we need public static void main string args,
为了运行代码，我们需要
public static void main(String[] args)
something like that, whatever that thing is.
像这样的东西
So that's our first program.
这就是我们的第一个程序
So we're going to built in a little more complicated, but just wanted to get that off our chest.
我们会加进一点复杂的东西，但需要先写出来这些
This is our basic Hello world program.
这就是基本的 Hello world 程序
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）